const AI_quiz1 = [
    {
        "question": "He coined the term Artificial Intelligence at the Darthmouth Conference",
        "options": [
            "Paul McCarthy",
            "John McCarthy",
            "Bryan McCarthy",
            "Chad McCarthy"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "John McCarthy"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is the theory and development of computer systems able to perform task that normally require human intelligence?",
        "options": [
            "General Intelligence",
            "Narrow Intelligence",
            "Artificial Intelligence",
            "Superior Intelligence"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Artificial Intelligence"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is the computational part of the ability to achieve goals in the world",
        "options": [
            "Emotion",
            "Will",
            "Rational",
            "Intelligence"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Intelligence"
    },
    {
        "question": "Doing the right thing that which is expected to maximize goal achievement, given the available information.",
        "options": [
            "Human Behavior",
            "Intelligent Behavior",
            "Rational Behavior",
            "Cognitive Behavior"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Rational Behavior"
    },
    {
        "question": "Humans as observed from 'inside'",
        "options": [
            "Systems that think like Humans",
            "Systems that act like Humans",
            "Systems that think Rationally",
            "Systems that act Rationally"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Systems that think like Humans"
    },
    {
        "question": "Humans are not always 'rational' or logical",
        "options": [
            "Systems that think like Humans",
            "Systems that act like Humans",
            "Systems that think Rationally",
            "Systems that act Rationally"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Systems that think Rationally"
    },
    {
        "question": "For the agent to do the right thing",
        "options": [
            "Systems that think like Humans",
            "Systems that act like Humans",
            "Systems that think Rationally",
            "Systems that act Rationally"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Systems that act Rationally"
    },
    {
        "question": "This was a giant animated bronze warrior who was programmed to guard the island of Crete.",
        "options": [
            "Janus",
            "Telus",
            "Talos",
            "Telos"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Talos"
    },
    {
        "question": "He created the Turing Test. This test is basically used to determine whether or not a can think intelligently like a human being.",
        "options": [
            "Allain Turing",
            "Alan Turing",
            "Allan Turing",
            "Alvin Turing"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Alan Turing"
    },
    {
        "question": "The year that the word Artificial Intelligence was coined.",
        "options": [
            "1954",
            "1959",
            "1956",
            "1952"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1956"
    },
    {
        "question": "The first Robot was introduced by which company?",
        "options": [
            "General Electronics",
            "General Motors",
            "General Merchandise",
            "General Kenobi"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "General Motors"
    },
    {
        "question": "An award given annually since 1990 to the most human-like computer program as voted by a panel of judges.",
        "options": [
            "Lobster Prize",
            "Nobel Prize",
            "Loebner Prize",
            "French Prize"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Loebner Prize"
    },
    {
        "question": "The first chatbot to have 'allegedly' passed the Turing Test.",
        "options": [
            "Smarter Child",
            "Eugene Goostman",
            "Google Duplex",
            "Siri",
            "Alexa"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Eugene Goostman"
    },
    {
        "question": "An Artificial Intelligent Assistant that can respond to calls and book appointments for you.",
        "options": [
            "Smarter Child",
            "Eugene Goostman",
            "Google Duplex",
            "Siri",
            "Alexa"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Google Duplex"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the very First Chatbot?",
        "options": [
            "Rollo Carpenter",
            "Kenneth Colby",
            "Joseph Weizenbaum",
            "Ron Hamilton"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Joseph Weizenbaum"
    },
    {
        "question": "PARRY, a program that imitated a patient with schizophrenia, was created by?",
        "options": [
            "Rollo Carpenter",
            "Kenneth Colby",
            "Joseph Weizenbaum",
            "Ron Hamilton"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Kenneth Colby"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Jabbarwacky was aimed to simulate a natural human conversation, and was created in 1992 by ______",
        "options": [
            "Rollo Carpenter",
            "Kenneth Colby",
            "Joseph Weizenbaum",
            "Ron Hamilton"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Joseph Weizenbaum"
    },
    {
        "question": "A chatbot created by Creative Labs for MS-DOS in 1992",
        "options": [
            "JABBERWACKY",
            "ALICE",
            "ELIZA",
            "DR SBAITSO"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "DR SBAITSO"
    },
    {
        "question": "A chatbot created by Creative Labs for MS-DOS in 1992",
        "options": [
            "JABBERWACKY",
            "ALICE",
            "ELIZA",
            "DR SBAITSO"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "DR SBAITSO"
    },
    {
        "question": "It answers questions, performs actions requests made to a set of web services and recommendations",
        "options": [
            "Siri",
            "Cortana",
            "Alexa",
            "Google Assistant"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Google Assistant"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is an intelligent personal assistant and navigator that uses a natural language UI",
        "options": [
            "Siri",
            "Cortana",
            "Alexa",
            "Google Assistant"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Siri"
    },
    {
        "question": "It became directly integrated into both phone devices and Windows 10 PCs",
        "options": [
            "Siri",
            "Cortana",
            "Alexa",
            "Google Assistant"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cortana"
    },
    {
        "question": "is now built in to devices such as the Echo, the Echo Dot, the Echo Show and more",
        "options": [
            "Siri",
            "Cortana",
            "Alexa",
            "Google Assistant"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Alexa"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Chess Player that IBM's Deep Blue defeated in 1996",
        "options": [
            "Sergey Karjakin",
            "Alexander Grischuk",
            "Veselin Topalov",
            "Garry Kasparov"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Garry Kasparov"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the very First Chatbot?",
        "options": [
            "Rollo Carpenter",
            "Kenneth Colby",
            "Joseph Weizenbaum",
            "Ron Hamilton"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Joseph Weizenbaum"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the first checker program known as Ferranti Mark 1 Machine in 1951?",
        "options": [
            "Christian Strachey",
            "Christopher Strachy",
            "Christian Harvey",
            "Christopher Strachey"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Christopher Strachey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the first chatbot created in 1966?",
        "options": [
            "Elisa",
            "Eliza",
            "Elise",
            "Elize"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Eliza"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is to retrieve and answer questions using stored information.",
        "options": [
            "Machine learning",
            "Automatic Reasoning",
            "Automated Reasoning",
            "Knowledge Representation"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Automated Reasoning"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created Jabberwacky?",
        "options": [
            "Rollo Carpenter",
            "Rollo Dishwasher",
            "Richard Wallace",
            "Christian Carpenter"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Rollo Carpenter"
    },
    {
        "question": "    If your task is of a larger scale than usual, and you have enough money to cover up the cost, you can opt for a GPU cluster and do ______________. ",
        "options": [
            "GPU clustering",
            "CPU clustering",
            "Multi-GPU computing",
            "GPU computing"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Multi-GPU computing"
    }
]


i